Hey guys, I wanted to make a quick video
大家好，我想快速制作一个视频，
going over a massive change in the
介绍一下更新补丁说明中的一个重大变化
updated patch notes. In fact, this is
。 事实上，这
probably the biggest change in the
可能是整个补丁中最大的改动，
entire patch and which is not released
而且直到现在才发布
until now. So, here it is. Crafted
。 好了，就是这样。 现在，原本只能给物品
methods that put a single guaranteed
添加一个固定
modifier on an item now adds as a
词缀的制作方法，会同时添加一个
crafted modifier. Items only have a
制作词缀。 物品
single crafted modifier on an item. This
上只有一个制作词缀。 这
is a massive nerf to power on items. the
是对强力装备的一次巨大削弱。
overall massive player crafting nerf.
玩家整体制作能力大幅削弱。
So, if you don't know what this is, if
所以，如果你不知道这是什么，如果
you're not really familiar, what are
你不太熟悉，
these modifiers? Essentially, there's a
这些修饰语是什么呢？ 从本质上讲，
lot of items in the game that give
游戏中有很多物品
guaranteed modifiers in an item when use
在用于制作时可以保证物品带有属性加成
for crafting. So, the ones that I assume
。 所以，我推测
this will count for is the regal essence
这应该算在内的是皇家精华
and the perfect essence. These both say
和完美精华。 这两个词都说
guaranteed modifier, uh the new imbued
保证有修改器，呃，新的注入
alloys. So, the new crafting method to
合金。 所以，
enter this patch, these an alloys, these
本次更新引入的新制作方法，这些合金，
should also count as a guaranteed
也应该算作一种保证的
modifier. So, you won't be able to combo
词缀。 所以，你无法将
these with the essence that we currently
这些与我们目前
have. and the new distills as well which
拥有的精华组合使用。 以及用于酿造的新型蒸馏酒
is also used for crafting. The big thing
。 关键在于
here is that it should be both regal
它既要体现王者之
essence and perfect essence. So you know
气，又要体现完美之气。 所以你知道，既有
both like the one we use for magic to
我们用来制作
rare and then also the perfect one as
稀有魔法道具的，也有完美的
well. So for example as a spellcaster
。 例如，作为一名施法者，
you want to be able to add a guaranteed
你希望能够将保证造成的
spell damage into a guaranteed plus
法术伤害添加到保证造成的额外
spells. Then for stuff like bows,
法术中。 然后还有弓、
crossbows, staffs, all that right
弩、棍棒之类的东西，以及所有右手
quarter staffs. I mean a very popular
棍棒。 我的意思是，一种非常流行的
crafting method was to get a magic base
制作方法是获得
with percent fizz. Then you'll use a
带有百分比起泡效果的魔法基底。 然后，你需要使用
greater essence of abrasion for flat
更强的摩擦力来制造平淡的
fizz. then you're fil of suffix like you
气泡。 那么你就像你
know plus of all skills plus uh chance
知道的后缀一样，加上所有技能，再加上
of on kill. Now all three of these
击杀时的机会。 现在这三者
should count as a single guaranteed
应该算作一个有保障的
modifier. So you cannot use all three.
修正值。 所以你不能同时使用这三种方法。
That means if you just use your flat
也就是说，如果你只用你的
essence that's it. You cannot craft any
精华液，那就够了。 你的弓箭无法再制作任何东西了
more in your bow. I mean you could of
。 我的意思是，你当然
course still use exalted orbs plus chaos
仍然可以使用崇高石和混沌
orbs but you cannot use the perfect
石，但你不能再使用完美
essence anymore. So stuff that won't
精华了。 所以，有些东西
count. Now we do need confirmation from
不算数。 现在我们需要
GG. This is quite a big change. So, you
GG的确认。 这是一个相当大的变化。 所以，你
know, I would have liked if GG does do
知道，我希望GG能
some confirmation on what does and
确认一下哪些算数，哪些
doesn't count. But I think abyss
不算数。 但我认为坠入深渊
crashing should not count. At least I
不应该算在内。 我
hope it doesn't count because it's not a
希望这不算数，因为这并非
guaranteed outcome. It is a random
必然的结果。 这是一个随机
modifier. The new Aldo rune crashing
修正值。 由于新的 Aldo 符文
we're getting since it requires you to
需要
chaos or span for the modifier. This
混沌或跨度来获得修饰符，因此我们遇到了崩溃问题。 这
should be a random modifier. And
应该是一个随机修正值。
hopefully the res swap that we're also
希望我们即将获得的资源交换
getting does not count. It would be kind
不算在内。 它算是熟的
of cooked. A res swap did count as a
。 资源交换确实算作一种
guaranteed modifier. But yeah, these are
保证生效的修正。 但是，这些
things that shouldn't count. And I
事情不应该被计入。 我
assume the new distills, new imbued
猜想，新的蒸馏酒、新的浸渍
alloys, and regal and perfect essence.
合金，以及尊贵完美的精华。
These should all count as guaranteed
这些都应该算作保证生效的
modifiers. And you cannot stack these on
修正值。 而且它们不能叠放在一起
top of each other. So what crafted
。 那么，究竟是哪种精心设计的
method does hurt the one I just went
方法会损害我刚才提到的方法呢
over? Easily. Weapons. Weapons. You
？ 容易地。 武器。 武器。
always use multiple essence modifiers on
在赛季初期，你总是会使用多个精华词缀
League Launch. Even like very high-end
。 即使是像高端
weapons, you use multiple essence. And
武器这样的武器，也需要使用多种精华。 而
now this is all just, you know, nerfed.
现在这一切都被削弱了。
You can no longer do this. This also
你不能再这样做了。 这也
does make some weapons a lot harder to
使得某些武器的制作难度大大增加
craft. For example, if you want to make
。 例如，如果你现在想制作
a crit bow now, essentially you get
一把暴击弓，基本上你只需要获得
percent fizz, maybe use a crit essence
百分比的起泡效果，可能再使用一个暴击精华，就完成了
and that's it. So you have to like
。 所以你必须像
unveil flat fizz with a abyss modifier
揭开深渊修饰符一样揭开扁平的嘶嘶声，
and then you know this perfect exalt the
然后你知道这个完美升华
last prefix and perfect exalt the last
最后一个前缀和完美升华最后
two suffix. Usually a very high-end
两个后缀。 通常情况下，只有非常高端的
weapon would be using it as extra
武器才会将其用作额外的
essence. So you do something like this
精华。 所以，你可以通过类似这样的
as extra fizz to get the last prefix and
额外操作来获取最后一个前缀，但
that won't be doable now, right? So
现在这已经不可能了，对吧？ 是的
yeah, this does hurt weapons quite a
，这确实会对武器造成相当大的损害
bit. It is a pretty big weapon nerf.
。 这是一次相当大的武器削弱。
Like honestly on league start I feel
说实话，我觉得
your league start weapons cuz you cannot
赛季初期武器的伤害平均会降低 30% 到 40%，因为你无法
combine all these essence anymore. Like
再合成所有这些精华了。
this combination of essence right here
这种精华组合在
was a very very common one for league
赛季初期武器中非常非常常见
start weapons. Use this for your last
。 将此用作最后一个
prefix. Use this for your second prefix.
前缀。 将此用作第二个前缀。   请将此用作
Use this for your suffix. And use this
后缀。 并以此
for your suffix. Right? So you plus
作为你的后缀。 正确的？ 所以你加上
three guaranteed fizz guaranteed as
三个保证气泡，保证
extra and guaranteed onslaught. And now
额外赠送，保证猛攻。 现在
you can only use one of these. So yeah,
你只能使用其中一个。 所以，没错，
it it is a pretty hefty nerf, especially
这确实是一次相当大的削弱，尤其是
for leaks on our weapons. I do expect
考虑到我们武器的泄露问题。 我预计
weapons to be a lot less powerful early
武器在游戏初期威力会大大降低，
on since now you're just going to have
因为现在你只需要
to exalt Slam and Prey. Yeah, that's
强化猛击和猎杀技能即可。 嗯，
about it. Of course, it does hurt other
差不多就是这样。 当然，这也会影响其他
crafted methods as well, but weapons are
制作方法，但武器受到的
definitely the biggest nerf here because
削弱最大，因为武器
they are the ones that always used
总是需要
multiple essences for a lot of, you
多种精华来进行很多
know, crafts. Let me know what you think
制作。 请在下方留言告诉我你的想法，你认为
down below if this is a good change or
这是一个好改变还是
bad change. I am kind of surprised that
坏改变。 我很惊讶
this was like a lastminute change and it
这是临时做出的改动，而且之前也
wasn't mentioned anywhere else because I
没有任何地方提到过，因为我
do feel like this is probably the
觉得这可能是
biggest change in the patch notes itself
补丁说明中最大的改动，
and definitely does hurt player power
而且肯定会对玩家的实力
and crafting quite a bit because you
和制作能力造成相当大的影响，因为你
know you won't be able to use all the
知道你将无法同时使用所有的
new stuff together like the new imbued
新东西，比如新的注魔
alloys you cannot use with essence
合金就不能再和精华一起使用了
anymore. I saw it.
。 我看到了。